I'm going to go public with something
that I thought I was going to take to my
grave.
Something that happened to me a couple
years ago or few years ago when I was in
college.
Um just be warned.
This is very serious.
It's traumatic.
And I don't mean to come on here and
and, you know,
make a video where I'm trying to scare
everybody. It's not about that.
It's not about trying to scare
everybody. This is just dead serious.
Yeah, so a few years ago I was in
college.
And at that time I was having a lot of
spiritual warfare, really bad.
Um I was struggling with uh corn really
bad. You guys know what I mean by that.
Um anyways,
one night I went to bed.
And
God took my
I It was in a dream. I God took my
spirit out my body.
And put me where I'm about to tell you.
I ended up in a
I I I knew I somehow I knew
that I was
thousands of feet beneath
the earth.
Like I was like towards the center of
the earth. I just knew that. He just put
it in me to know that. I can't explain
it. Um some people are going to know
what I'm talking about. He doesn't
audibly speak. You just He just inside
He just tells you.
Anyways, I ended up in this cave, very
long hallway, sheer rock, thick rock all
around me.
Very thick.
And
um
I was experiencing God allowed me in
certain moments to experience what they
were what I'm about to tell you, what
people were experiencing down there.
So, the first thing that happened was
to my left, Jesus let me know that there
was a guy in a room. He's about 20 ft
deep into the rock. So, realistically,
I'm only about 30 ft away from him, but
he don't know that.
Jesus told me this guy was in his 30s
and he was a rock climber in this life.
That's all that I know.
And he was being tormented
in that tiny room
forever.
He was I can hear him
sobbing and saying, "Help me.
Um I can't get out of here." Stuff like
that.
So much dread, so much anxiety, and so
much fear he was experiencing. He wasn't
on fire, but
uh
it was
just an immense amount of fear, and I
was able to slightly feel that cuz God
allowed me to.
And what I What God also didn't allow
was for me to feel how much heat was in
that area. For some reason the Lord
who's being gracious and did not allow
me to feel that.
But he was being tormented and he's not
getting out. So, he's being tormented in
that one little area
of no hope, fear, and anxiety. Like, you
know how we get those feelings on earth?
It's I can't even explain to you
how much further that could go.
I know a lot of us have anxiety for
whatever reason and fear. We all
experience that to some extent, but down
there
it you can't even compare it. You
There's no pill.
There's You can take 1 million pills of
anxiety meds and that still cannot get
you out of that situation or that
feeling. You can't. I just knew that.
Anyways,
moving on, I walked a little bit further
and I heard a woman scream so loudly.
And it was like the most death-defying
scream in agony, uh uh
scared, fear, hopelessness.
And the Lord actually allowed me to
experience just a part of what she was
feeling.
But when she screamed, the first time
she screamed,
it pierced through my chest into my
bones. It made my whole body start
convulsing as if I was having a seizure.
And all I knew is that she was in her
30s. I don't know what she did on in
this life. I don't know what she did to,
you know, I don't know. That's all he
let me know.
Um
if someone were to ask me, "What is the
most fear you've ever experienced in
your life?" It wasn't here. It was in
that moment.
Nothing in this life, no movie, no
almost getting hit by a car, uh I've had
a couple seizure in the seizures in this
lifetime. Nothing can compare to that
moment, how scared it would It shot It
shoots to your soul, your soul.
And
I was shaking.
And then after that, she was being
tormented. And then after that, he took
away those feelings so that I can focus
on something else. And I looked
at the end of the hallway and there was
a portal, giant 12-ft by 10-ft portal.
And I knew, cuz he told me, that's the
lake of fire.
That's the portal to the lake of fire.
So, they're not in the lake of fire.
They're just in
hell before they get to the lake of
fire. People that know that know that.
And um
I just I just couldn't believe that
there was a woman down there. I just had
a hard time accepting that there was a
woman
down there in hell. I For some reason I
could not
accept that.
Like, Lord, is there's a There's women
down here? You got to be kidding me.
Um
So, first off, I want to say that the
Lord was not mean
by showing me this. He was not being
like
whatever you you would think
humanly speaking coming up with an idea
of like, "Oh, God did that to" No. He
was doing that cuz he was showing me
reality. That's reality.
We're either going there or we're going
there.
Period. Those people will not get out. I
hate saying that. Those people will not
get out.
They won't get out.
Anyways, when I When he put my spirit
back in my body and I awoke,
it was like a flashbang went off in my
eyes. It was all white. I was shaking
uncontrollably. I had to It took me
about 4 minutes to gain all of my fluids
and everything back. I don't know how to
explain it. And I had to freaking learn
how to rewalk. I know it sounds stupid.
I had to learn how to rewalk.
Excuse me.
By myself in my room at like
probably between 3:00 and 5:00 a.m. in
the morning.
And I'm telling you guys this because
hell and heaven, they are real places.
We are spirits that are in this human
flesh body. And one day,
excuse me,
we're going to go there or we're going
to go there.
I have never went public with this. I
was never going to go public with this.
And again, I don't mean to scare you,
but if this drives you towards at least
looking at the Bible, looking towards
Jesus,
that's that's what I'm going for.
Because it is not a joke.
Um
He was being gracious to me by showing
me that.
And I'm going to be honest, it took me
probably until last year to come to
terms with what he showed me. Because it
was absolutely
terrifying. I would never wish the
amount of fear that I felt in that
moment when she screamed. I I don't even
wish that upon the person that I don't
like the most here.
I don't want anybody to experience that.
Um this is really important.
Take it seriously.
He knows that you're not perfect. He's
not looking for perfection. He's looking
for your heart. He's looking to change
your mind and your heart.
It takes a while.
But yeah.
Um
I I will try to keep I've been getting a
lot of DMs lately and I suck at getting
back to people. I'm really trying to get
back to people.
Um
guilty of that. Uh but I will try to
keep my DMs open so you guys could um if
you have any questions. This was really
hard for me to talk about.
Um because I don't like No one likes to
talk about hell. No one That That's just
the reality. Anyways,